Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 18, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Korzybski, Alfred, 1879-1950
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter on scientific views.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 6, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Krevin, L M
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of an article.
  - Statement to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Nov. 26, 1941; Lancaster Press
    Lancaster, Typed D. 3 items. Various sizes (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Pertaining to reprints from the APS Proceedings.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 11, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lawton, Shailer Upton, 1894-1966
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for an article in a publication, devoted to education.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 7, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lawton, Shailer Upton, 1894-1966
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning publications on education.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 17, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lawton, Shailer Upton, 1894-1966
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 18, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lawton, Shailer Upton, 1894-1966
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 10, 1923; 9x6; Leidy, Joseph, 1866-1932
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards drawing.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec., 1923; 9x6; Leidy, Joseph, 1866-1932
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends drawing by Leidy.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 17, 1924; 9x6; Leidy, Joseph, 1866-1932
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 19, 1924; 9x6; Leidy, Joseph, 1866-1932
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 14, [1924?]; 8x5; Leidy, Joseph, 1866-1932
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 2, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lillie, Frank Rattray, 1870-1947
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 26, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert), b. 1887
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Yale university will not object to his repeating lectures elsewhere.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, August 10, 1932; 11x8-1/2; Lovejoy, P S
    Ann Arbor, Typed L. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug.15, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Loveman, Amy
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 4, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Loveman, Amy
  - Letter to Jerome Alexander, New York, July 31, 1944; 11x8-1/2; Lynch, Ruth Jennings Stocking, 1887-
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards reprint pages sent in error to H.S. Jennings.
  - Letter to Byrle Jacob Osborn,Waltham, Mass., Jan. 28, 1947; 11x8-1/2; Lynch, Ruth Jennings Stocking, 1887-
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards Jennings's permission that he may quote a passage from a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 4, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Lynn, Ida M
    New York, Typed L.S 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to H.S. Jennings, Jan. 13, 1945; 11x8-1/2; MacDougall, Mary Stuart, b. 1885
    Los Angeles; Decatur, Ga., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to reproduce a photograph. Scientific news.
  - Letter to H.E. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 31, 1945; 11x8-1/2; MacDougall, Mary Stuart, b. 1885
    Decatur, Georgia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his picture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 20, 1924; 11x8-1/2; MacDowell, E. Carleton (Edwin Carleton), 1887-1973
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publications concerning immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] s. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 23, 1939; 11x8-1/2; MacNider, William de Berniere, 1881-1951
    Chapel Hill, N.C., Typed L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a group to study aging.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 2, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Mann, Delbert M
    Lawrence, Kansas, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 9, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Marshall, Mrs. Janet L
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business from Yale university press.
  - Certificate of membership to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Sept. 1, 1915; 8-1/2x11; Maryland league for national defense
    Baltimore, Printed D.filled in in ms.S.: H. Findlay French. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Berkeley, Oct. 4, 1940; 11x8-1/2; McCarthy, Daniel J. (Daniel Joseph), 1874-1958
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1P.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lecture at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angles, Jan. 2, 1941; 8-1/2x5-1/2; McCarthy, Daniel J. (Daniel Joseph), 1874-1958
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprint.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 3, 1946; 10-1/2x7-1/4; McCarty, Coralie
    Urbana Ill., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Letter describing how much his publications has aided her.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 13, 1939; 11x8-1/2; McCormick, Patrick J. (Patrick Joseph), b. 1880
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Glad he will contribute to the publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Sept. 15, 1944; 11x8-1/2; McCulloch, Irene Agnes, b. 1886
    A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 27, 1934; 11x7; McGee, Lemuel Clyde, 1902-
  - Notes on current events, March 4, 1934; McGee, Lemuel Clyde, 1902-
    Mimeographed D.S. 1p.and 2 pamphlets. Various sizes. Add. to H.S.Jennings(?) (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 11, 1940; 10-1/2x8; McGraw, Myrtle B. (Myrtle Byram), 1899-
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to use an illustration from one of his publications.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jeennings, July 31, 1946; 11x8-1/2; McKee, Ruth Karr, b. 1874
    Typed L. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his kindnesses.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 24, 1934; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publications.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 23, 1928; 11x8-1/2; Metcalf, Henry C. (Henry Clayton), 1867-1942
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Asks concerning some lectures.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 7, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Metcalf, Maynard M. (Maynard Mayo), 1868-1940
    Waban, Mass., Typed L.S. 1p.and enc. of 5p. (see H.S Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Encloses essays.
  - Letter to H[erbert S.], Jennings, Feb. 2, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Metcalf, Maynard M. (Maynard Mayo), 1868-1940
    Waban, Mass., Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 11, 1930; 10-1/2x8; Metzler, William H. (William Henry), b. 1863
    Albany, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Asks question in genetics.
  - Letter to Herbert [S.] Jennings, Baltimore, March 21, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Meyer, Adolf Frederick, 1880-
    Baltimore, Typed L.D. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 22, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Meyer, Adolf Frederick, 1880-
    Baltimore, (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 12, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Miles, R E
    Columbus, O., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a possible bill for the sterilization of the feeble-minded.
  - Letter to Virginia R. Wing, Cleveland, Sept. 12, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Miles, R E
    Typed L. 5p. Copy. Enc.of bill of 5p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning sterilization of the feeble-minded. Quotes H.S. Jennings on the subject.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 22, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Moore, Barrington, 1883-
    New York, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 24, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Moore, J. Percy (John Percy), b. 1869
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lecture at the U of P bicentenneal celebration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 6, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Moore, J. Percy (John Percy), b. 1869
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Hopes he will participate in the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 15, 1923; 10-1/2x8; Moore, J. Percy (John Percy), b. 1869
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the speech he is to make on Leidy.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 13, 1934; 7x4-1/2; Morgan, C. Lloyd (Conwy Lloyd), 1852-1936
    A.L.S. 1p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 13, 1934; 7x4-1/2; Morgan, C. Lloyd (Conwy Lloyd), 1852-1936
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, [1930?]; 10x8-1/2; Mullenix, Rollin Clarke, 1869-
    Appleton, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Compliments on his book. Refers to Conklin.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 5, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Mulligan, Margaret E
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb.25, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Nash, Jay Bryan, 1886-1965
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 3, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Nash, Jay Bryan, 1886-1965
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 2, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Nash, Jay Bryan, 1886-1965
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Hopes he will write an article on education.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 11, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Nash, Jay Bryan, 1886-1965
    New York, Typed L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks help in preparing a publication on education.
  - Diploma of membership issued to Herbert Spencer Jennings, April 23, 1914; 15-1/2x19-1/2; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.)
    Printed D.filled in in ms.S.: William H. Welch, pres.,W.D.Walcott, vice pres., and Arthur L. Day and George E. Hale, secs. 1p. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 21, 1931; 11x8-1/2; National Committee for Mental Hygiene
    New York, Typed L.S.: Margaret Wagenhals. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 11, 1931; 11x8-1/2; National Committee for Mental Hygiene
    New York, Typed L.S.: Margaret H. Wagenhals. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Questions a statement of a publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], April 24, 1940; 11x8-1/2; National Research Council
    Washington, Typed L.S.: Ione M. Seafield. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Notifies him of date of committee meeting.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, April 9, 1940; 11x8-1/2; National Research Council
    Washington, Typed L.S.: R.E. Coker. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Hopes to hold committee meeting.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 13, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Neal, Herbert V. (Herbert Vincent), 1869-1940
    Tufts college, Mass., Typed L.S. 2p.and enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Conference on the interpretations of physical education, March 30-April 1, 1933; 11x8-1/2; New York University
    D. 49. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) One speech is to be by Dr. Jennings.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 22, [1944-1946?]; 10-1/2x7; Nin, Man-Chiang
    Stanford, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 16, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Norton, W W
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 4, 1931; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Norton, W W
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 25, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Offermann, Carlos A
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning genetics.
  - Letter to H.S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 20, 1947; 11x8-1/2; Osborn, Byrle
    Waltham, Mass., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to quote a passage from one of his publications.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, May 17, 1923; 10-3/4x8-1/4; Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1857-1935
    New York Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 19, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Osterud, Hjalmar Laurits, 1883-
    Richmond, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will be glad to help with speeches.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 15, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Osterud, Hjalmar Laurits, 1883-
    Richmond, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning equipment for speeches.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 10, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Osterud, Hjalmar Laurits, 1883-
    Richmond, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will provide equipment for speeches.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 5, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Osterud, Hjalmar Laurits, 1883-
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 25, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Osterud, Hjalmar Laurits, 1883-
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 4, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Pack, Charles Lathrop, 1857-1937
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his speech on Leidy.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Oct. 1, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Park, Thomas, 1908-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the possible publication of articles.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 21, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Park, Thomas, 1908-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article for publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 4, 1942; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Park, Thomas, 1908-
    Chicago, A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends scholarly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Feb. 16, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Park, Thomas, 1908-
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 30, 1930; 10-1/2x8; Parker, George Howard, 1864-1955
    Cambridge, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Congratulates him on his book.
  - Letter to [Herbert Spencer] Jennings, May 11, 1943; Peabody, James E
    Typed L.S. 1p.and enc.of photograph, 2 printed items. 1 mimeographed item on yellow fever, and 1p.copy of F.S.Conant. Various sizes. (see H.S.Jennings papers) Concerning Williams college members, especially F.S.Conant and N.R.Harrington. For photograph, see print collection
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 18, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will forward material on Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 8, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 8, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, April 12, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, May 24, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 2, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning business of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, June 4, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 29, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 3, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning Raymond Pearl's ancestry.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 4, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 7, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his memoir on Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 10, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his memoir on Raymond Pear].
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 12, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his memoir on Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 18, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a plate for use in a memoir of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 22, 1942; 8x5; Pearl, Maud M. DeWitt
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning photograph and plate of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 24, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Pearl, Raymond, 1879-1940
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the immigration problem.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 22, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Pearl, Raymond, 1879-1940
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 8, 1933; 7-1/4x5-1/2; Peebles, Florence, 1874-
    Altadena, Cal., A.L.S. 3p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 22, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Perkins, Henry Farnham, 1877-
    Burlington, Vt., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 6, 1924; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Perkins, Henry Farnham, 1877-
    Burlington, Vt., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publications.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], [1927]; 10-1/2x6-1/2; Plain talk
    New York, Typed L.S.: G.D. Eaton. 1p. Enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Asks for subscriptions and encloses form for ordering.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 6, 1946; 11x8-1/2; Pomeroy, Fred Elmer, 1877-
    Lewiston, Maine, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks concerning his book, "Genetics".
  - Account with H[erbert] S. Jennings, Feb. 1, July 31, 1939, 1945; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Princeton University Press
    D. 3 leaves, end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Statement to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 1, 1942; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Princeton University Press
    Princeton, Typed D. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 13, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Prior, W.F., company, inc.
    Hagerstown, Md., Typed L.S.: J.A. Mitchell. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a new edition of a book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 22, 1941; 10-1/2x7-1/4; Prior, W.F., company, inc.
    Hagerstown, Md., Typed L.S.: L.W. Manners. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Concerning a new publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 22, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Procter, William, 1872-1951
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning one celled organisms.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 6, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Procter, William, 1872-1951
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Oxford, Eng., Jan. 31, 1936; 11x8-1/2; Progressive Education Association
    New York, Typed L.S.: Frances M. Foster. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 10, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Queen, Stuart Alfred, 1890-1987
    Lawrence, Kansas, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 1, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Raphael, Theophile, 1891-
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for statistics dealing with Jewish immigration.
  - Letter to Faber & Faber, Ltd., Dec. 10, 1930; 7x4-1/2; Rasbridge, W J
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a possible error in Jennings book. Enclosed originally in letter from Faber and Faber to H.S.Jennings; Dec.15, 1930.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 2, 1930; 8x6-1/2; Revista de Occidente
    Madrid, Typed L. 1p.,end. In French. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes to translate into Spanish his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Nov. 28, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Rhoades, Marcus M. (Marcus Morton), 1903-1991
    New York, A.L.S.on postal card. 1p.and add.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Concerning his article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 12, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Richmond, Hotel
    Richmond, Typed L.S.: G.E.Williams. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Has reserved room for him.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 31, 1923; 7-1/4x5-1/2; Riddle, Marjorie
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 10, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Ritter, William Emerson, 1856-1944
    Berkeley, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S[pencer] Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 26, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Robinson, Elliott Stirling, b. 1894
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks to quote one of his articles.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S[pencer] Jennings, Baltimore, March 30, 1923; 11x8-1/4; Robinson, Elliott Stirling, b. 1894
    Chicago, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a quotation from one of his publications.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 28, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Sanford, Edmund C. (Edmund Clark), 1859-1924
    Worcester, Mass., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprint on immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan.7, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Sanford, G B
    Edmonton, Canada, Typed L.on postal card,S. 1p.,end.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 15, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Schoen, Max, 1888
    Pittsburgh, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks question concerning education.
  - Telegram to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, Aug. 17, 1940; 10x8; Science Service
    Washington, Telegram S.: Watson Davis. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to speak on science on radio.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 8, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Scott, Joseph M
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 10, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Scott, Joseph M
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like for him to speak to their organization.
  - Letter to [Herbert S. Jennings], May 13, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Seafield, Ione M
    Typed L.S. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article in German.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 26, 1928; 11x8-1/2; Searle, William D
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 26, 1941; 10-1/2x7-1/4; Sexson, Paul A
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Jan. 17, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Shapovalov, Leo, 1908-1994
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint.